what's going on ladies and gentlemen
welcome back to another one as you can
see we're on the water we're in the
Pontoon today we're going to be doing
some fishing but along with that we're
doing another product review on a reel
that I'm super excited to talk about
it's the PC fun Viper X now I just got
this thing in the mail and let me tell
you it looks slick this thing is awesome
it's black with green finishes and this
thing is very appealing to the eye I'm
super excited to try and catch a fish
with it today we're going to talk about
it break it down and tell you guys what
I think about it so stay tuned let's get
to the action all right so we're just
throwing a little weightless senko Texas
Rig this is probably one of my more
favorite ways to catch fish in the
summertime there's a lot of bass in this
Lake but we're going to kind of break
down how what we think of this reel and
just off of my first initial cast very
smooth I mean that was pretty Precision
your bail here opens super easily and
closes super easily it's not hard to
close it or anything like that hopefully
we can hook up on some fish I do I'm
running a 20 lb braid and it feels super
super smooth it reels super smooth and
it's very very lightweight these are
just kind of my first initial thoughts
on this thing but let's try and get into
a little bit of cover let's see how
accurate we can throw it so the Viper X
the PC fun Viper X this reel it's a 621
gear ratio which is pretty standard I
think a lot of the reels come in that
gear
ratio and there's 10 ball bearings and
an extra so there's 11 ball bearings in
this bad boy and let me tell you what it
feels very smooth I mean it doesn't it
hardly makes any noise when you reel it
it's so smooth I must say I'm pretty
impressed with that I've used their
carbon X's before and honestly for the
price point I feel like this one is
almost I mean it's a little bit cheaper
man it it is smooth PC funds really
outdid themselves with this one I love
the design I love the green and I
believe you can get this in a purple as
well but I think the green just looks so
cool with some with some green braid on
there it looks awesome really can't
complain about it anything
there oh must have been a weed oh you
know what nope that was a
fish
dang see if we can find that guy again
or if we spooked
him the casting power on this thing I
mean I'm just throwing a weightless Seno
and you can really Chuck it out there
that was like not even half power and I
could throw it a lot farther so that's
pretty
exciting I really like the braided line
on here I'm not really sure how it would
with mono or fluorocarbon but I imagine
that it would be pretty awesome um if
you guys do like this re if you like the
look of it you can check it out on PC
fund's website I'll leave a link in the
description you can save 15% if you use
my code jj15 as well so check them out
if you want I don't think you'll regret
it my first overall reaction is this
thing's pretty sweet you can definitely
tell that the 11 bearings is awesome in
this thing this is the 2000 size reel
2000 is kind of my go-to for everything
just
for just for to give yourselves a little
sense of how big this reel is it uh the
braided line it says you can put 15 lb
braided line and it'll hold 15 yards or
you can put an 8 lb mono and it'll hold
120 yards so that gives you a little bit
of a gauge for how big the Reel is and
honestly that's more than enough line
for most things that you're fishing for
in fresh water I'm going to give this a
real hard cast just so you guys can see
the distance I can get on this thing and
I'm I'm casting straight into the wind
here but I bet you I can get some pretty
good distance I mean that's way up there
that's pretty dang good I did kind of
let go a little late there but you can
get some real distance on this thing the
drag sounds awesome I don't know if you
can hear
that but it sounds super cool that
clicking just sounds awesome definitely
kind of gets you riled up when you're
reeling a big fishing cuz you can
definitely hear that drag ripping no
doubt about that so the one thing about
this reel it does have a foam handle I
do like the foam because it keeps the
Reel lighter and worse case you know if
if for for some reason the foam ever did
break you can replace them super easily
so you know not really a worry there I
kind of like the feel of the foam grip
too it just is always soft and feels
nice in your hand so I wouldn't really
change that I like that they do that to
their reels and I think it I think it
makes them pretty nice the drag you just
tighten and loosen the drag on the top
like usual there is a reverse line
switch right here so you can run your
reel backwards and forwards I don't
really ever do anything with that mostly
just always leave it like that and good
good to go um but you can if for some
reason you wanted to you can does have
that
option I might have to find a spot to
tuck out of the wind a little
better let's
see I'm going to try and hit maybe I can
hit that point up there let's see if
it's too
far yeah too far all in all I think this
reel definitely meets my expectations I
love adding more PC fun reels into the
into the mix of the real that I have
because so far every single one that
I've gotten is just absolutely awesome I
can't say good enough things about it I
mean look at that thing it reels so
smooth there's absolutely nothing I
would change about
it I love the design they really do
something cool with their designs of
their reels cuz they look just unlike
anything else I mean most the reels you
buy from the store you know they're just
gray or white or something like that but
this black and green throw a little
different colored uh throw some colored
line on there and man it looks cool
I paired it up with the Abu Garcia
Vengeance it's a medium action Rod 7 ft
and it feels like a really good combo
for this this Rod I like it um all in
all though guys I don't really think
there's anything bad I can say about
this it casts good the drag is good you
can turn you can crank this drag way
down too I mean almost to the point
where yeah I can't even oh I can't even
pull it out if I loosen it a little bit
there I mean that's probably easily 20
lb of drag or more I don't know I don't
know exactly but that's a lot of drag so
if you're if you're wanting to throw
like a 30 or 40 lb braid on here and
pull fish across the top of the water I
mean you can do that with this thing too
um I think it would make a great
allaround fishing fishing reel for you
know just about anything in the midwest
here or down south or wherever you're at
you know we fish for a lot of bass
Northern walleye crappie I think you
could do all of it with this so all in
all though guys I like it if you any
other questions make sure to leave a
comment down in the description and uh I
hope you guys enjoyed the video and if
you did make sure to subscribe to the
channel and like the video and we'll see
you guys in the next one peace